♪ Ohh naa naa ♪
♪ Omo je ka shi ge ge whoa ♪
♪ Omo ge wa j'ogede, whoa ♪
♪ Ohh naa naa ♪
♪ Girl I no go let you go ♪
♪ Omo je ka shi ge ge whoa ♪
♪ Say I wanna leave you in the
mornin' ♪
♪ But I need you now,
yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I find you, I give you all
you needin' ♪
♪ I know you what you like ♪
♪ I feel it comin' ♪
♪ Time is of the essence ♪
♪ I tried to teach you ♪
♪ But I might need some
lessons ♪
♪ I need to give it all ♪
♪ I tried to leave but
I can't ♪
♪ I don't know why, you're
the one ♪
♪ Turn me out of my mind ♪
♪ You don't need no
other body ♪
♪ Only you fi hold my body ♪
♪ You don't need no
other body ♪
♪ Say na me dey mess up
your mind ♪
♪ And na me dey make you free
up your mind ♪
♪ Say your body talk to
me nice ♪
♪ Say na my love, you dey need
for your life ♪
♪ Yeah our love no be lie ♪
♪ See yeah we dey together yeah
day and night ♪
♪ Yeah if I leave you
go kpai ♪
♪ Yeah if you leave I
go kpai (oh, oh whoa) ♪
♪ I'm strokin' your body, baby
Lovin' your body, baby ♪
♪ As you're whinin' your body,
baby, so crazy ♪
♪ Lovin' your body, baby
Gyal iwo ni temi ♪
♪ I just wanna let you know,
ohh ♪
♪ Hope every day that I
dey by you ♪
♪ You don't need no
other body ♪
♪ Only you fi hold my body ♪
♪ You don't need no
other body ♪
♪ Baby, baby ♪
♪ Everybody used to say ♪
♪ No one loves you
like this ♪
♪ No one wants you the
same way ♪
♪ Love 'til the mornin' ♪
♪ My head wan' to turn from
your lovin' ♪
♪ I just wanna get you
beside me ♪
♪ Gave you all you need, gave
you all you need ♪
♪ Gave you all, you give me all
you need ♪
♪ Give you all you need,
gave you all ♪
♪ Make I give you
all you need ♪
♪ Every touch you need,
give you all ♪
♪ Make I give you all you need,
baby ♪
♪ Yeah-yeah, yeah-yeah
You don't need no other body ♪
♪ You don't need no
other body ♪
♪ Only you fi hold my body ♪
♪ Only you fi hold my body
(yeah-yeah, yeah-yeah) ♪
♪ You don't need no other body
Baby girl I want you there ♪
♪ Girl I want you there ♪
♪ Promise to treat your
love fair ♪
♪ Whoa-whoa, whoa-whoa ♪
♪ When we touch,
how we connect ♪
♪ Whoa-whoa, whoa-whoa ♪
♪ Said this love,
have no regret ♪
♪ Whoa-whoa, yeah-yeah ♪
♪